gigapros.com 2019-02-05

# Privacy Policy | GigaPros.com

## GigaPros Respects Your Privacy

At GigaPros we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use GigaPros' services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard your information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

At GigaPros, the customers' information including personal contact information and server data is treated with strict confidentiality and will not be shared with anyone. GigaPros collects cookies on our web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally to improve the content we provide to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. If you choose to communicate to us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact our webmaster.

## Extent of Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to how we gather, utilize, and reveal information from the following individuals: 

**Clients** – people who sign up, by themselves or in the interest of another entity, to utilize GigaPros Services with the creation or administration of a GigaPros account. 

**Events/Marketing Participants** – people who share their personal data with GigaPros when they enroll for GigaPros webinars, subscribe to advertising materials, take an interest in surveys, or attend different GigaPros digital events. 

**Site Visitors** – people who visit GigaPros’s Website and opt to give contact details including email addresses to receive emails from GigaPros. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, a Website Visitor does who visit a site hosted by GigaPros but owned and maintained by a GigaPros’s customer, is not included. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to a customer's site. Our Customers are in charge of the data they or their end clients stores on our servers and are compliant with the applicable laws and regulations, and GigaPros' Terms of services. 

## Information We Collect

**Clients** GigaPros requests for your account information which contains your name, business name, email address, physical address, telephone number, Mastercard and bank account information (stored with an outsider processor), and website domain. By willfully giving GigaPros your information, you own and adhere to our use of such personal data. 

**Events/Marketing Participants** GigaPros may request your name, email address, physical address, and telephone number. Participating in events, surveys or subscribing to marketing material is voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose your personal data. 

**Site Visitors** With your option, GigaPros asks and may gather your name, email address, physical address, and telephone number. Additionally we gather data, for example, web server logs, IP addresses, browser information, or other data as a feature of collected information. 

## How We Use your Information

GigaPros utilizes the data it gathers about you in the following ways: 

  * To reply back to any requests from you regarding sales and support
  * To contact you in regards to any agreements or acknowledged terms that you may have with GigaPros for the Services.
  * To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters.
  * To give you data logs related to the utilization of GigaPros's Services.
  * To get in touch with you in regards to usefulness changes to our Services or Website.
  * To collect bill and payment for our Services.
  * To analyze issues.
  * To discover and avoid misrepresentation.
  * To complete different purposes as revealed to you through the Website, or found in agreement or an understanding amongst you and GigaPros.
  * Process for different purposes for which we acquire your assent. 

## How We Share Information

GigaPros shares the data it gathers about you in the following ways: 

**Outsider Providers** – GigaPros may impart your data to outsider suppliers that provide services on our behalf or resellers who provide GigaPros Services. These organizations may help with showcasing support, handling credit card payment, content conveyance, email, giving providing sales leads, and customer support. Outsider suppliers may just process individual data according to GigaPros’s directions, and consistency with the Privacy Policy and other applicable regulations. 

**Domain Registrars** \- The domain owner’s data (WHOIS Records) for any domain name is required and controlled by the ICANN-accredited registrars and the Registry for the TLD (Top-level domain) which you wish to register. We share your data to the extent which is necessary to comply by the ICANN's guidelines, directions and policies, with principles and arrangements by the ICANN-licensed registrars we represent and the standards and approaches of the top-level domain Registry. These registrar providers are located in USA and Canada. The information is also shared with the Registry for the top-level domain which may be located in another jurisdiction. The use and disclosure of the personal information as part of the domain registration process is governed by the applicable agreements with the ICANN-accredited registrar. 

**Consent** \- With your explicit consent or at your direction we may share and disclose information related to you that you have authorized us to with third parties. We will not, however, sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose any personal identifiable information for commercial purposes in any way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

We use Cookies to collect some of the information mentioned in this Policy. A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in your web browser on your computer, mobile or other browsable devices, while you are visiting a website. 

Our Site uses cookies to identify you. Cookies can store your ordering status, identify your account. Cookies can also be used for technical purposes such as keeping track of your current shopping session or to save information which has already been entered (languages choices, and your region), so that we can offer improved and more personalized services and products which are tailored for you. Cookies also allow us to fulfill our contractual obligations to third parties and partners if you have made a purchase on our website by following a link from theirs. For more information on Cookies, click [here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). 

You can control how websites use cookies by changing your cookie settings straight from your browser. Please note that if you simply disable all of our cookies or cookies in general in your browser settings, you may find that certain sections or features of our Site will not work, because your browser may prevent us from setting Site functionally required by cookies.

## Purposes of Data Processing

When you access or use our Services, we need to collect, use, and otherwise process your information, as set out in this Policy. We are committed to your privacy and follow a few fundamental principles when we process personal data: 

We strive to collect only the minimum personal data that we need to deliver any Services to you. 

We aim for full transparency on how we use your information to comply with legal or other lawful purposes and respect your privacy. 

We make sure we only use your information for the purposes you have given us permission for. 

We rely on a number of legal bases to use your information, as set out in this Policy: 

**Contract** – the use of your information is necessary to perform any contractual obligations in order to provide any Services to you or to administer any Contests you enter into; 

**Legal obligations** – our use of your personal information is necessary to comply with a legal obligation, a court order, or to exercise or defend legal claims. For example, if we are requested to disclose your personal information to regulatory bodies or law enforcement authorities; or to use your personal information for tax calculations. 

**Our legitimate interests** – necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests, such as to: 

  * run, grow, develop and deliver our services;
  * detect and prevent fraudulent activities;
  * enhance the security of our network and information systems;
  * better understand how people interact with our website;
  * determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and advertising; and
  * enhance, modify, personalize or otherwise improve our services and communications for the benefit of our customers.

**Consent** – we rely on your consent for us to use your personal information to send you marketing information (such as our newsletters and promotional offers) by email, SMS, or telephone. You may withdraw your consent at any time by updating your personal Info/Settings in your user profile in our User Area

## International Transfers

We host, store or otherwise handle your personal information within the borders of European Economic Area (EEA) and the USA. 

We will make sure that any transfers of your personal information from one country to another comply with thе data protection and privacy laws that apply. 

European data protection laws, in particular, include specific rules on transferring personal information outside the EEA. 

When transferring personal information outside the EEA to the USA, we will include the standard data protection clauses approved by the European Commission under Article 46.2 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) into our contract with GigaPros and our other Partners. 

You can find out further information about the rules on data transfers outside the EEA, including the mechanisms that we rely upon, on the European Commission website [here](https://www.gigapros.com/portal/terms-and-conditions/privacy-policy/data-processing-addendum/). 

In any event, your information will be processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you would like further information about the global handling of your personal information, please contact us on our email [support@gigapros.com](mailto:support@gigapros.com).

## Age Restrictions

Our Website and/or Services is not directed at children and our services are designed for businesses. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age, and use of our services by children under 13 years of age is forbidden.

## Changes To Privacy Policy

GigaPros reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, however, should we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the changes, you may terminate your Services.

## Opt-Out Policy

Our customers and users will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information on products, services, or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, GigaPros gives them the opportunity to opt-out from receiving these types of communications. 

If do not wish to receive our newsletter, promotional communications or any other non-service related communication, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [support@gigapros.com](mailto:support@gigapros.com) or you may contact us at 1-877-PRO-GIGA or via written mail by sending a letter to our **postal address** , to opt-out. 

On some occasions, it may be necessary to send out service-related announcements. In most cases, users may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may deactivate your account by creating a cancellation request ticket in your hosting control panel, or by emailing us at [cancel@gigapros.com](mailto:cancel@gigapros.com) or by contacting us at 1-877-PRO-GIGA or via written mail by sending a letter to our **postal address** , to opt-out.

## Contact Us

If you have additional questions, please **contact us** at any time. You can also drop us a postal mail addressing to "Customer Privacy Department". **Click here** to see our postal address.
